Hey, I'm Walter, your instructor.
مرحبًا، أنا المعلم والتر.
After learning all the cool things you can do with code,
بعد أن تعلمتم عن كل الأشياء الرائعة التي يمكنكم فعلها باستخدام الكود،
writing documentation might seem a bit stale.
قد تبدو كتابة التوثيق مملة بعض الشيء.
I'm here to show you why that's, in fact, not the case and
أنا هنا لأوضح لكم أنّ هذا ليس حقيقيًا في الواقع
why you should get excited about documenting your code.
وأنّكم ستشعرون بالحماس عند توثيق الكود.
In this course you'll be cooking up your very own readme file.
في هذه الدورة التعليمية، ستقومون بإعداد ملفكم التمهيدي الخاص.
You'll learn what documentation is and
ستتعلمون ما هي حقيقة التوثيق
why it's an important part of the development process and
وسبب اعتباره جزءً مهمًا في عملية التطوير
you'll be able to incorporate it into your projects moving forward.
ستتمكنون من دمجه في مشروعاتكم المتقدمة.
This course is relevant to anyone who either writes code or
تتعلق هذه الدورة التدريبية بأي شخص إما يكتب الأكواد
works with others who do.
أو يعمل مع آخرين يكتبونها.
Throughout this course, you'll be seeing examples of documentation for
طوال هذه الدورة التدريبية، سترون أمثلة على توثيق
a variety of tools and languages, some will be familiar and others will not.
مجموعة متنوعة من الأدوات واللغات، بعضها مألوفة والأخرى لا.
That's okay.
حسنًا.
Focus on the concepts, not the actual code that we'll be documenting.
ركزوا على المفاهيم، لا على الكود الفعلي الذي ستعملون على توثيقه.
To help us get started, I've cooked up a little something for you.
لقد أعددت شيئًا صغيرًا لكم ليساعدنا في البدء.
How does this relate to readme's?
ما صلة هذا الشيء بالملفات التمهيدية؟
Well, you'll understand in a minute.
حسنًا، ستفهمون بعد دقائق.